Finding Aid for the James G. Stahlman Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Vanderbilt University - Subject
  - Ransom, John C. (Box V-31, Folder 15)
  - Religious Emphasis Week (Box V-31, Folder 16)
  - Shore, Dinah (Box V-31, Folder 17)
  - $30 Million For Vanderbilt Campaign (Box V-32, Folder 1)
  - $30 Million For Vanderbilt Campaign (Box V-32, Folder 2)
  - $30 Million For Vanderbilt Campaign (Box V-32, Folder 3)
  - $30 Million For Vanderbilt Campaign (Box V-32, Folder 4)
  - $30 Million For Vanderbilt Campaign (Box V-32, Folder 5)
  - $30 Million For Vanderbilt Campaign (Box V-32, Folder 6)
  - $30 Million For Vanderbilt Campaign (Box V-32, Folder 7)
  - $30 Mllion For Vanderbilt Campaign (Box V-33, Folder 1)
  - $30 Million For Vanderbilt Campaign (Box V-33, Folder 2)
  - Unions (Box V-33, Folder 3)
  - Vanderbilt Family Visit (Box V-33, Folder 4)
  - Vanderbilt Hustler (Box V-33, Folder 5)
  - Vanderbilt Television News Archives (Box V-33, Folder 6)
  - Vanderbilt University Hospital & Medical Center (Box V-33, Folder 7)
  - Vanderbilt University Hospital & Medical Center (Box V-33, Folder 8)
  - Veterans Hospital (Box V-33, Folder 9)
  - Weapherby, Harold L. (Box V-33, Folder 10)
- Vanderbili University - Publications
  - Publications, AGB Reports - “American Philanthropic Foundations” (Box V-34, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Centennial Symposium on... (Box V-34, Folder 2)
  - Publications, Code or By Laws - Danforth News & Notes (Box V-34, Folder 3)
  - Publications, “Educational Value of.. .” - For Alumni (Box V-34, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Ford Foundation Annual Report - “Graduate Schools.. .” (Box V-34, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Harvard Alumni Bulletin - Institute for American Strategy (Box V-34, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Landon Cabell Garland ... - Observations On... (Box V-35, Folder 1)
  - Publications, Prospectus - Reserve... (Box V-35, Folder 2)
  - Publications, The Responsibility ... - “Statements by.. .” (Box V-35, Folder 3)
  - Publications, Status of Campus... Status Repo rt On... (Box V-35, Folder 4)
  - Publications, Status Report... - Vanderbilt Alumnus (Box V-35, Folder 5)
  - Publications, Vanderbilt Commodores - Vanderbilt vs. Georgia Tech (Box V-35, Folder 6)
  - Publications, Vanderbilt Voice - Wesley Notes (Box V-36, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Alumni Association (Box V-36, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Arambro-Gainza Paz Visit (Box V-36, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Board of Trust (Box V-36, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Board of Trust, 1945 - 1968 (Box V-36, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Board of Trust, 1970 - 1974 (Box V-36, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Board of Trust (Box V-36, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Centennial of the Founding of Vanderbilt University and Reunion of Descendants of Cornelius Vanderbilt (Box V-36, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, Class of 1916, Reunion (Box V-36, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, Comet West (Box V-36, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, Commodore Band (Box V-36, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, Dudley - Luton (Box V-36, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, Nrotc - “Negroes.. .” (Box V-36, Folder 13)
  - Photographs 1915 Football Team (Box V-36, Folder 14)
  - Photographs 1915 Football Team, Reunion (Box V-36, Folder 15)
  - Photographs 1915 Football Team, Reunion (Box V-36, Folder 16)
- Vanderbilt University - Photographs
  - Photographs, 1915 Football Team, Reunion (Box V-37, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, 1915 Football Team, Reunion (Box V-37, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, 1915 Football Team, Reunion (Box V-37, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Reyer, George W. (Box V-37, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Stahlman, James G (Box V-37, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Stahlman, James G, 1916 - 1931 (Box V-38, Folder 1)
  - Photographs, Stahlman, James G (Box V-38, Folder 2)
  - Photographs, Stahlman, James G (Box V-38, Folder 3)
  - Photographs, Stahlman, James G, undated & unidentified (Box V-38, Folder 4)
  - Photographs, Stahlman, John H. (Box V-38, Folder 5)
  - Photographs, Vanderbilt Family Visit - Vanderbilt, Harold S. (Box V-38, Folder 6)
  - Photographs, Vanderbilt - Navy Football Breakfast Game (Box V-38, Folder 7)
  - Photographs, Vanderbilt - Navy Football Breakfast Game (Box V-38, Folder 8)
  - Photographs, unidentified (Box V-38, Folder 9)
- Speeches
  - Speeches, May 11, 1915, R. A. Young Oratory Medal, Vanderbilt University (Box VI-1, Folder 1)
  - Speeches, Apr. 7, 1932, West End Men’s Club (Box VI-1, Folder 2)
  - Speeches, May 21, 1934, Convention of Southern Newspaper Publishers Association (Box VI-1, Folder 3)
  - Speeches, Apr. 23, 1937, American Newspaper Publishers Association (Box VI-1, Folder 4)
  - Speeches, Jun. 29, 1937, Conference of Joint Publishers (Box VI-1, Folder 5)
  - Speeches, Oct. 26, 1937, Eulogy for Edward H. Harris (Box VI-1, Folder 6)
  - Speeches, Apr. 27, 1938, American Newspaper Publishers Association (Box VI-1, Folder 7)
  - Speeches, Nov. 29, 1938, “A Free Press in a Democracy” (Southern States Industrial Council) (Box VI-1, Folder 8)
  - Speeches, Jan. 21, 1939, “A Free Press in a Democracy” (California Newspaper Publishers Association) (Box VI-1, Folder 9)
  - Speeches, Apr. 25, 1939, Dedication of Statue to the Freedom of the Press, New York World’s Fair (Box VI-1, Folder 10)
  - Speeches, Jul. 12, 1939, National Association of Broadcasters (Box VI-1, Folder 11)
  - Speeches, 1932-33, undated, Welcoming Greek Visitors to Nashville, TN - (Box VI-1, Folder 12)
  - Speeches, Feb. 19, 1940, Economic Club of Detroit (Box VI-1, Folder 13)
  - Speeches, 1940, undated, Nashville, TN (Box VI-1, Folder 14)
  - Speeches, Oct. 31, 1941, “Mr. Armistead, The Newspaper Associate & Friends”, Fifty Years in Business Club (notes) (Box VI-1, Folder 15)
  - Speeches, Dec. 6, 1941, Dedication of Joint Universities Libraries (Box VI-1, Folder 16)
  - Speeches, Dec. 15, 1941, Bill of Rights’ 150th Anniversary, Richmond, VA (Box VI-1, Folder 17)
  - Speeches, Nov. 11, 1945, “Old Sawney ~ The Citizen,” Webb School (Box VI-1, Folder 18)
  - Speeches, Feb. 7, 1946, Carmichael Dinner (Box VI-1, Folder 19)
  - Speeches, Mar. 10, 1946, West End Methodist Young Peoples Group (Box VI-1, Folder 20)
  - Speeches, Apr. 9, 1946, Belmont Methodist Church (Box VI-1, Folder 21)
  - Speeches, May 8, 1946, Boys Club Dinner in Memory of Tony Sudekum (Box VI-1, Folder 22)
  - Speeches, Oct. 16, 1947, “invincible Trinity”, Coffee House Club (Box VI-1, Folder 23)
  - Speeches, Oct. 27, 1948, James G. Stahlman Annual Navy Day Award, Vanderbilt University (Box VI-1, Folder 24)
  - Speeches, Nov. 26, 1948, Edwin Warner Park Ceremony (Box VI-1, Folder 25)
  - Speeches, Dec. 8, 1948, Tourist & Convention Bureau for Traffic Officers of Nashville, Davidson County & State of Tennessee (Box VI-1, Folder 26)
  - Speeches, Sep. 14, 1949, Salute to Fred Russell, WSM (Box VI-1, Folder 27)
  - Speeches, Sep. 14, 1950, Acceptance Speech: Board of Parks Commissioners Resolution (Box VI-1, Folder 28)
  - Speeches, Nov. 11, 1950, Armistice Day, Introduction & Memorial Plaque Unveiling (Box VI-1, Folder 29)
  - Speeches, 1950, undated, Amvets (Box VI-1, Folder 30)
  - Speeches, Apr. 8, 1951, Forward America program, WLAC (Box VI-1, Folder 31)
  - Speeches, Sep. 5, 1951, Distinguished Americans Series, 75th Anniversary Party of Banner (Box VI-1, Folder 32)
  - Speeches, 1951, undated, 75th Anniversary Party of Banner (Box VI-1, Folder 33)
  - Speeches, Nov. 18, 1952, Norman Vincent Peale Dinner (Box VI-1, Folder 34)
  - Speeches, Dec. 6, 1952, Dedication of Vanderbilt Gymnasium (Box VI-1, Folder 35)
  - Speeches, Jan. 17, 1953, Tennessee Society, Introduction of Frank Clement (Box VI-1, Folder 36)
  - Speeches, Sep. 8, 1953, Fred Russell, 25th Anniversary Dinner (Box VI-1, Folder 37)
  - Speeches, May 17, 1956, “Rough Road to Freedom,” Coffee House Club (Box VI-1, Folder 38)
  - Speeches, Sep. 38, 1956, Introduction of Richard M. Nixon as V. P. Candidate (Box VI-1, Folder 39)
  - Speeches, School News Conference; Birmingham, AL (Box VI-1, Folder 40)
  - Speeches, Jan. 19, 1957, Introduction of John S. Knight, AlianzaMan of the Year Award (Box VI-1, Folder 41)
  - Speeches, May 30, 1958, memorial Day, Nashville, TN (Box VI-2, Folder 1)
  - Speeches, Jun. 2, 1958, Note (Box VI-2, Folder 2)
  - Speeches, Jan. 12, 1960, Coosa River Newsprint Mill, 10th Anniversary (Box VI-2, Folder 3)
  - Speeches, Oct. 6, 1960, Introduction of V. P. Richard Nixon (Box VI-2, Folder 4)
  - Speeches, Jan. 11, 1961, Sam Fleming (Box VI-2, Folder 5)
  - Speeches, May 4, 1961, Vanderbilt Campaign Dinner Meeting (Box VI-2, Folder 6)
  - Speeches, Jan. 8, 1965, Andrew Jackson Day (Box VI-2, Folder 7)
  - Speeches, Jan. 24, 1966, Farewell to Cast of “Sing-Out ’66” (Box VI-2, Folder 8)
  - Speeches, Jul. 20, 1968, American Legion, 50th Anniversary Convention (Box VI-2, Folder 9)
  - Speeches, May 22, 1970, American Legion Headquarters Dedication (Box VI-2, Folder 10)
  - Speeches, American Legion, Fourth Estate Award (Box VI-2, Folder 11)
  - Speeches, Oct. 21, 1970, Al Menah Temple Masonic Dinner (Box VI-2, Folder 12)
  - Speeches, Dec. 4, 1971, Al Menah Ceremonial Class Named in JGS’s Home (Box VI-2, Folder 13)
  - Speeches, Oct. 18, 1975, Vanderbilt University, 50th Anniversary of 1915 Football Team (Box VI-2, Folder 14)
  - Speeches, undated, Eulogy for Vernon Southall Tupper (Box VI-2, Folder 15)
  - Speeches, undated, Impact of Technical Advances (Box VI-2, Folder 16)
  - Speeches, undated, Introduction of Gen. Clifton B. Cates (Box VI-2, Folder 17)
  - Speeches, undated, Tribute to Warner Brothers (Box VI-2, Folder 18)
  - Speeches, undated, Vanderbilt University Reunion (Box VI-2, Folder 19)
  - Speeches, undated, unidentified, notes (Box VI-2, Folder 20)
- Military and Aviation Careers - Correspondence
  - Outgoing (Box VII-1, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 10, 1930 - May 19, 1931 (Box VII-1, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 12, 1931 - Mar. 21, 1932 (Box VII-1, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 24 - Dec. 29, 1932 (Box VII-1, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 18 - Aug. 31, 1933 (Box VII-1, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 2, 1933 - Apr. 5, 1934 (Box VII-1, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 10 - Dec. 22, 1934 (Box VII-1, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 14 -Feb. 22, 1935 (Box VII-1, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 1 - Jul. 17, 1935 (Box VII-1, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 2 - Dec. 26, 1935 (Box VII-1, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 15 - May 27, 1936 (Box VII-1, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, May 28 - Oct. 1, 1936 (Box VII-1, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 3, 1936 - Jan. 9, 1937 (Box VII-1, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 25 - Sep. 27, 1937 (Box VII-1, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 16, 1937 - Apr. 21, 1938 (Box VII-1, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, May 2 - Sep. 20, 1938 (Box VII-1, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 11 - Dec. 22, 1938 (Box VII-1, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 2 - Jul. 19, 1939 (Box VII-1, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 19 - 25, 1939 (Box VII-1, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 26 - 30, 1939 (Box VII-1, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 1 - 3, 1939 (Box VII-1, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 4 - 7, 1939 (Box VII-1, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 8 - 16, 1939 (Box VII-1, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 4 - 13, 1939 (Box VII-1, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 16 - Dec. 30, 1939 (Box VII-1, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 2 - Oct. 28, 1940 (Box VII-1, Folder 26)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 21 - Dec. 31, 1940 (Box VII-1, Folder 27)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 3 - 29, 1941 (Box VII-2, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 9 - 12, 1941 (Box VII-2, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 15 - 22, 1941 (Box VII-2, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 1 - 16, 1941 (Box VII-2, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 17 - May 7, 1941 (Box VII-2, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, May 9 - Aug. 26, 1941 (Box VII-2, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 5 - Oct. 22, 1941 (Box VII-2, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 23 - Nov. 14, 1941 (Box VII-2, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 15 - 18, 1941 (Box VII-2, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 19 - 28, 1941 (Box VII-2, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 1 - 17, 1941 (Box VII-2, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 18 - 31, 1941 (Box VII-2, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 2 - 8, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 9 - 14, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 15 - 24, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 27 - Feb. 6, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 7 - 14, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 16 - Feb. 26, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 27 - Mar. 8, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 9 - 21, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 23 - Apr. 2, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 3 - 17, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 18 - 22, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 23 - 27, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 28 - May 21, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing, May 22 - 30, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 26)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 1 - 9, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 27)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 10 - Jul. 8, 1942 (Box VII-2, Folder 28)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 17 - Aug. 11, 1942 (Box VII-3, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 12-26, 1942 (Box VII-3, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 27 - Sep. 3, 1942 (Box VII-3, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 4 - 10, 1942 (Box VII-3, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 11 -26, 1942 (Box VII-3, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 28 - Oct. 7, 1942 (Box VII-3, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 8 - 23, 1942 (Box VII-3, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 24 - Nov. 7, 1942 (Box VII-3, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 9 - 16, 1942 (Box VII-3, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 16-20, 1942 (Box VII-3, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 21 -24, 1942 (Box VII-3, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 26 - Dec. 3, 1942 (Box VII-3, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 4 - 10, 1942 (Box VII-3, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 11 -21, 1942 (Box VII-3, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 22, 1942 - Jan. 7, 1943 (Box VII-3, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 8 - 18, 1943 (Box VII-3, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 20 - Feb. 6, 1943 (Box VII-3, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 9-22, 1943 (Box VII-3, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 23 - Mar. 9, 1943 (Box VII-3, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 10-22, 1943 (Box VII-3, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 23 - Apr. 19, 1943 (Box VII-3, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 19 - May 4, 1943 (Box VII-3, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, May 5 - 15, 1943 (Box VII-3, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, May 17 - May 29, 1943 (Box VII-3, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 26, 1943 - Jan. 13, 1944 (Box VII-3, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 17 - Apr. 1, 1944 (Box VII-3, Folder 26)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 29 - Oct. 27, 1944 (Box VII-3, Folder 27)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 1, 1944 - Jan. 1945 (Box VII-4, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 4 - 26, 1945 (Box VII-4, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 30 - Feb. 28, 1945 (Box VII-4, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 5 - Apr. 9, 1945 (Box VII-4, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, April 18 - Jun. 18, 1945 (Box VII-4, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 27 - Aug. 21, 1945 (Box VII-4, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 24 - Sep. 28, 1945 (Box VII-4, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 15 - Nov. 20, 1945 (Box VII-4, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 3 - 19, 1945 (Box VII-4, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Dec. 20 - 31, 1945 (Box VII-4, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 2 - 10, 1946 (Box VII-4, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 14 - Mar. 8, 1946 (Box VII-4, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 11 - May 4, 1946 (Box VII-4, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, May 9 - Dec. 20, 1946 (Box VII-4, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 4 - Oct. 17, 1947 (Box VII-4, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 20 - 31, 1947 (Box VII-4, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 3, 1947 - Aug. 31, 1948 (Box VII-4, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 1 - Oct. 29, 1948 (Box VII-4, Folder 18)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 1 - Apr. 11, 1949 (Box VII-4, Folder 19)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 13 - Jun. 24, 1949 (Box VII-4, Folder 20)
  - Outgoing, Jul. 3 - Sep. 23, 1949 (Box VII-4, Folder 21)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 23 - Oct. 12, 1949 (Box VII-4, Folder 22)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 14 - 21, 1949 (Box VII-4, Folder 23)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 22 - 28, 1949 (Box VII-4, Folder 24)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 29 - Nov. 23, 1949 (Box VII-4, Folder 25)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 25 - Jan. 12, 1950 (Box VII-4, Folder 26)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 13 - Jun. 20, 1950 (Box VII-5, Folder 1)
  - Outgoing, Jun. 23 - Jul. 31, 1950 (Box VII-5, Folder 2)
  - Outgoing, Aug. 3 - Dec. 29, 1950 (Box VII-5, Folder 3)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 2 - Mar. 21, 1951 (Box VII-5, Folder 4)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 22 - Nov. 8, 1951 (Box VII-5, Folder 5)
  - Outgoing, Nov. 12, 1951 - Jan. 9, 1953 (Box VII-5, Folder 6)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 15 - Sep. 28, 1953 (Box VII-5, Folder 7)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 3, 1953 - Sep. 7, 1954 (Box VII-5, Folder 8)
  - Outgoing, Sep. 14, 1954 - Feb. 29, 1956 (Box VII-5, Folder 9)
  - Outgoing, Mar. 1 - Oct. 9, 1956 (Box VII-5, Folder 10)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 10, 1957 - Jul. 9, 1958 (Box VII-5, Folder 11)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 20, 1959 - Dec. 31, 1962 (Box VII-5, Folder 12)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 21, 1963 - Mar. 28, 1967 (Box VII-5, Folder 13)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 3, 1967 - Sep. 27, 1972 (Box VII-5, Folder 14)
  - Outgoing, Oct. 23, 1972 - Feb. 4, 1974 (Box VII-5, Folder 15)
  - Outgoing, Feb. 18, 1974 - Mar. 31,1975 (Box VII-5, Folder 16)
  - Outgoing, Apr. 1 - Dec. 30, 1975 (Box VII-5, Folder 17)
  - Outgoing, Jan. 2 - Apr. 28, 1976, undated (Box VII-5, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Abbott - Abraham (Box VII-5, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Adam - Aiken (Box VII-5, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Akers - Alexander (Box VII-5, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Allen, Arthur A. (Box VII-5, Folder 22)
  - Incoming, Allen, Arthur A. (Box VII-5, Folder 23)
  - Incoming, Allen, Arthur A. (Box VII-6, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Allen, Arthur A. (Box VII-6, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Allen, Arthur A. (Box VII-6, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Allen, G. - Anderson, A. (Box VII-6, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Anderson, E. Robert (Box VII-6, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Anderson, H. - Anderson, N. (Box VII-6, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Anderson, P. - Anderson, T. (Box VII-6, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Anderson, W. - Appleton (Box VII-6, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Arends - Armstrong (Box VII-6, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Ash worth - Baker (Box VII-6, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Baldridge - Barker (Box VII-6, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Barnes - Baruch (Box VII-6, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Bate - Beal (Box VII-6, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Beal - Beaverbrook (Box VII-6, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Beck - Beecher (Box VII-6, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Behncke - Berlin (Box VII-6, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Bernrieder, William A. (Box VII-6, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Bernrieder, William A. (Box VII-6, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Bernrieder, William A. (Box VII-6, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Bernrieder, William A. (Box VII-6, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Bernrieder, William A. (Box VII-6, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Berquist, Blackie (Box VII-6, Folder 22)
  - Incoming, Blanchard - Blethen (Box VII-6, Folder 23)
  - Incoming, Boddy - Booth (Box VII-7, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Border - Bowler (Box VII-7, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Bowles - Brandon (Box VII-7, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Braxton - Brooks (Box VII-7, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Browder - Brownstein (Box VII-7, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Bruce - Bunker (Box VII-7, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Bunnelle - Burke (Box VII-7, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Burt - Butler (Box VII-7, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Byrd (Box VII-7, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Byrns - Caldwell (Box VII-7, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Calhoun - Carden (Box VII-7, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Carey - Carter (Box VII-7, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Cassady - Cayce (Box VII-7, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Chairman - Cheek, R. (Box VII-7, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Cheek, W. - Chief (Box VII-7, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Christy - Clagett (Box VII-7, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Clark - Cleveland (Box VII-7, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Gift - Commandant (Box VII-7, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Commander - Conolly (Box VII-7, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Cook - Copeland (Box VII-7, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Corcoran - Cornwell (Box VII-7, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Corson - Cowles (Box VII-8, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Cox - Crawford (Box VII-8, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Creighton - Creyke (Box VII-8, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Crockett - Crommelin (Box VII-8, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Crosley - Dapping (Box VII-8, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Davis - Dawson (Box VII-8, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Dealey - Denfeld (Box VII-8, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Denig - Dillon (Box VII-8, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Dinsmore - Dondero (Box VII-8, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Donovan - Dougla (Box VII-8, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Douglass - Drum (Box VII-8, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Duchein - Duke (Box VII-8, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Duncan - Dyer (Box VII-8, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Earle - Ellender (Box VII-8, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Eller, E. M. (Box VII-8, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Ellinger - Epstein (Box VII-8, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Erickson - Evans (Box VII-8, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Everett - Ezelle (Box VII-8, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Faerber - Farrar (Box VII-8, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Farrington - Field (Box VII-8, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Fielding - Floyd, H. F. (Box VII-8, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Floyd, J. P. - Folk (Box VII-9, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Follis - Fort (Box VII-9, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Poster, B. - Poster, P. (Box VII-9, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Poster, P. (Box VII-9, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Poster, P. - Poster, W. (Box VII-9, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Foust - Frank (Box VII-9, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Franklin - Friendly (Box VII-9, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Frierson - Furry (Box VII-9, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Gaffhey - Gaylord (Box VII-9, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, General - Gillett (Box VII-9, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Glantzberg - Gracey (Box VII-9, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Graham - Guitian (Box VII-9, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Guild - Gwathmey (Box VII-9, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Hackney - Hall (Box VII-9, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Halladay - Hare (Box VII-9, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Harkins - Hart (Box VII-9, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Harter - Hayes, E. A. (Box VII-9, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Hayes, W. C. - Hebert (Box VII-9, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Hecht - Heermance (Box VII-9, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Heffernan - Henderson, G. (Box VII-9, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Henderson, R. - Henszey (Box VII-9, Folder 21)
  - Incoming, Henthorne - Hickman (Box VII-9, Folder 22)
  - Incoming, Hicks - Hobby (Box VII-10, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Hodges - Home (Box VII-10, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Horton - Howard (Box VII-10, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Howe - Hudson (Box VII-10, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Hunt, J. (Box VII-10, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Hunt, John (Box VII-10, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Hunt, John - Hutchison (Box VII-10, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, Imes - Jacobs, J. (Box VII-10, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, Jacobs, Ranoall (Box VII-10, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, Jacobs, Ranoall (Box VII-10, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, Jagger - Jicamenav (Box VII-10, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, Johannessen - Johnson, M. (Box VII-10, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, Johnson, W. (Box VII-10, Folder 13)
  - Incoming, Johnston - Jordan (Box VII-10, Folder 14)
  - Incoming, Kabler - Kerby (Box VII-10, Folder 15)
  - Incoming, Kemey - Kirchhofer (Box VII-10, Folder 16)
  - Incoming, Kirkland - Knowland (Box VII-10, Folder 17)
  - Incoming, Knox (Box VII-10, Folder 18)
  - Incoming, Koehn - Kuster (Box VII-10, Folder 19)
  - Incoming, Labounty - LaRoche (Box VII-10, Folder 20)
  - Incoming, Larson - Leahy (Box VII-11, Folder 1)
  - Incoming, Leath - Leslie (Box VII-11, Folder 2)
  - Incoming, Lester - Levine (Box VII-11, Folder 3)
  - Incoming, Levy - Lipslomb (Box VII-11, Folder 4)
  - Incoming, Little - Lord (Box VII-11, Folder 5)
  - Incoming, Losar - Lovejoy (Box VII-11, Folder 6)
  - Incoming, Lovett - Lyle (Box VII-11, Folder 7)
  - Incoming, McAuliffe - McClelland (Box VII-11, Folder 8)
  - Incoming, McClure - McDonald (Box VII-11, Folder 9)
  - Incoming, McDowell - McGugin (Box VII-11, Folder 10)
  - Incoming, McGuire - McKellar (Box VII-11, Folder 11)
  - Incoming, McKercher - McNeil (Box VII-11, Folder 12)
  - Incoming, McNicholas - Macy (Box VII-11, Folder 13)